sitecube.com 2016-12-11

# Free Website Builder, Build a Website Easily!

## Privacy Policy

**SiteCube** has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

1. Information Collected During Your Use of the SiteCube Service In order to register, users are required to give us contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in our records 

If you decide to purchase SiteCube's "Designer Website Builder", SiteCube will need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address ("Financial Information"). Financial Information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for other purposes. SiteCube does not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with it's Solutions.

2\. Our Use of Your Information

We use customer contact information from the registration form to send you information about SiteCube and promotional material from some of our partners. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We may use your IP address to help protect our partners and us from fraud. 

3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

SiteCube will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business' personally identifiable information to any third party. 

4\. Security

In order to maximize the protection of your information, SiteCube' Service uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet.

5\. General

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the 

. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please [contact us](http://www.sitecube.com/contact.html). 

Copyright © 2006-2016 SiteCube.com All rights Reserved.

## Privacy Policy

**SiteCube** has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

1. Information Collected During Your Use of the SiteCube Service In order to register, users are required to give us contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in our records 

If you decide to purchase SiteCube's "Designer Website Builder", SiteCube will need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address ("Financial Information"). Financial Information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for other purposes. SiteCube does not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with it's Solutions.

2\. Our Use of Your Information

We use customer contact information from the registration form to send you information about SiteCube and promotional material from some of our partners. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We may use your IP address to help protect our partners and us from fraud. 

3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

SiteCube will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business' personally identifiable information to any third party. 

4\. Security

In order to maximize the protection of your information, SiteCube' Service uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet.

5\. General

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the 

. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please [contact us](http://www.sitecube.com/contact.html).
